The pattern on that medicine bottle is exquisitely crafted.
It shouldn't be the work of an ordinary artisan.
I've already sent someone to investigate the totem.
Are you feeling unwell?
I told you earlier.
Your injury hasn't healed yet.
First, rendezvous with Royal Sister and the others.
Rest for two days before seeking Qin Chi.
You just wouldn't listen.
It's fine.
The mysterious person is in the shadows.
Finding Qin Chi must be done quickly.
Besides, Zi Xiu's injury still needs a few days of rest.
Have some water.
Did you pull on the wound?
Here.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Let me feed you.
It's all wet.
My Lord.
This subordinate has ordered a message sent to inform Fourth Princess.
That you and Fifth Princess went to find Qin Chi first.
Understood.
A Zi, what are you looking at?
Cousin sent a letter.
What does the letter say?
We must gather all three Secret Keys.
To open the Secret Gate's Forbidden Ground.
Only then can we decipher the secrets of the Map of the Nine Provinces.
Now, Qing Chi's Secret Key is already in hand.
Two remain now.
They are in the hands of Qin Chi and Jian Chi, respectively.
He and A Lan went to find Qin Chi first.
Did he say where?
He didn't.
However, Cousin's letter says...
Qin Chi dislikes conflict.
The Secret Key shouldn't be hard to obtain.
You drink this medicine first.
A Zi.
Actually, my injury is already of little consequence.
This medicine...
I won't drink it.
No.
Then...
I'll wait for this medicine to cool before drinking it.
The doctor said...
Medicine must be drunk while hot.
But this medicine is very bitter.
Yes.
Good medicine is bitter to the taste.
A Zi.
Did you encounter a quack doctor?
After I finish this medicine...
I feel weak all over.
My limbs are stiff.
How can this be?
Could it be...
I misread the prescription?
A Zi.
Next time, tasks like brewing medicine...
You should leave them to the attendants at Ren'an Tang.
Is it really that bitter?
Opera scripts say...
There's another method to relieve bitterness.
Not enough.
A Zi.
I will never let you go.
Candied hawthorn berries!
Come buy candied hawthorn berries!
Sugar figurines! Come, have a taste!
Sugar figurines! Come, miss, take a look!
Thank you.
Hurry up.
Is it good?
You try some.
Fresh watermelon!
Miss, my readings are very accurate!
No need.
Wait for me a moment.
I'll be right back.
Your side hustle has even expanded to Dongyang City.
What side hustle?
This Drama Spirit has been waiting for you here for a long time.
Speak.
What is it?
I have good news to tell you.
What good news could you possibly have?
Congratulations.
The mission to save the immortal herb was successful.
Successful?
Now, that Cold Epiphyllum Immortal Herb...
is growing quite vigorously.
No way.
A mere cutting can come back to life?
I can only say you're lucky.
I'd rather not have this damn luck.
Since when has A Lan been interested in this?
Just playing around casually.
A very bad fortune, miss.
Your romantic fate...
You must look carefully.
The young master's reminder is correct.
Upon this careful look...
This fortune is very auspicious!
Miss, in the future, you will surely have three husbands and four lords.
Your household will be harmonious!
Aren't you going to do something?
You brought this on yourself.
Let's go.
Three husbands and four lords...
Very happy.
What?
Are only you men allowed three wives and four concubines...
and we women not allowed three husbands and four lords?
Just think about it.
If the household is harmonious...
Make way, make way!
I, Yuwen Rui...
in this life, will only grow old with one person.
Heavens divine, earth divine!
Fortune-telling and divination, I'm the most accurate!
Yin Yang, Five Elements, ten divinations, nine accurate!
If not accurate, no charge!
My Lord.
This subordinate has not found Qin Chi's trail.
Only know that every year on this day, the qin masters of Dongyang City...
gather at the Elegant Lodge in the east city to meet friends through qin music.
Qin Chi is obsessed with the qin as if his life depends on it.
He is sure to appear.
Go wait for him to show up.
Let's go.
My Lord
Since we need to find three secret keys
to uncover the secret on the treasure map
Why don't I send someone to find Yuwen Rui
to see if we can learn where Qin Chi is?
No need.
Since Yuwen Rui has made the first move,
we'll let them do the dirty work
and then we'll be the ones to profit.
My Lord...
An Kezi trusts you completely now.
Why don't we use her life
to threaten Yuwen Rui? How dare you!
My Lord!
You cannot let personal feelings
hinder our great undertaking!
Since when do you get to
tell me what to do?
If you dare touch her,
don't blame me for being ruthless.
Do you understand?
This subordinate understands.
The secret key in Jian Chi's possession
must be obtained before Yuwen Rui gets it.
Yuwen Rui will eventually figure out
what the pattern on the medicine bottle means.
Notify our people in the palace to begin preparations.
It's time to reclaim the Map of the Nine Provinces.
Yes.
This old master's skill is superb.
Excellent, excellent, excellent.
Truly marvelous! Absolutely wonderful!
Indeed.
Can you tell
who plays the qin best?
They're equally matched.
Qin Chi's qin skills are exceptional.
If he's among them,
he'll surely hide his true ability.
Why don't I give it a try?
Find a way to make him slip up.
In my opinion, this qin master plays best.
What do you know?
Young lady...
What are you...
I'm sorry.
I haven't eaten for days.
I'm feeling a bit weak.
You still need to eat.
She can play the qin too?
Look at her posture.
Everyone,
I, a humble woman, have traveled far,
and am now completely penniless.
Today, hearing you gather here to meet through music,
I thought to find a destined owner for this qin
to exchange for some silver.
This qin looks rather ordinary.
How much silver do you want for it, miss?
Ordinary?!
You...
You dare call this qin ordinary?
Do you know this qin is...
Could it be this qin has a story?
This qin...
Forget it.
Today, I might as well tell you all.
Have any of you heard of
Shadow Gate's Qin Chi?
Qin Chi?
No, I don't know.
I've never heard of him.
Have you heard of him?
Shadow Gate... Qin Chi?
Who is Shadow Gate's Qin Chi?
Never heard of him in the jianghu.
Well, that's to be expected.
This person is elusive
and extremely skilled at hiding his identity.
It's normal you wouldn't know.
This qin...
Could it be related to that Qin Chi?
was Qin Chi's token of love to my aunt.
It's a family disgrace,
not fit for public airing.
But I'm truly at the end of my rope.
Years ago, Qin Chi pledged himself to my aunt.
But he left behind this ancient qin
and vanished without a word.
He didn't know...
my aunt...
had been...
waiting for him all this time!
She even carried his child for ten months and bore him a daughter!
This is truly absurd!
To think we have such a person among us!
For Qin Chi to act this way
is truly darn it!
Yes!
Too darn it!
Simply despicable!
He should be taught a lesson!
It's so infuriating!
My aunt just passed away early this year.
So I've been carrying this qin, searching for Qin Chi everywhere,
just to ask him on behalf of my late aunt
and my critically ill cousin:
"Do you still remember Xia Yuhe by the Daming Lake?"
For Qin Chi to love and then abandon her...
He's truly shameless!
Old sir,
don't you think that Qin Chi
is both callous and heartless?
My poor, critically ill cousin
still wishes to see her own father
one last time!
Calluses this thick...
Let's go.
Back home.
Miss,
did Qin Chi truly pledge himself to your aunt?
Your aunt had a hard life.
Indeed!
Let's beat him up!
Master!
There's really nothing!
Xia Yuhe by the Daming Lake!
That woman came for the secret key.
How many times must I say it?
I don't know her,
nor any Xia Yuhe!
Why such a big temper?
Master,
how did you know
they came for the secret key?
I received a letter from Qing Chi before.
He said he'd already handed over his secret key
and revealed clues to the other two keys.
I didn't expect
them to find me so quickly.
It seems what's meant to come will come.
There's no hiding from it.
Oh, it's my wife.
What nonsense are you spouting here?
Now everyone outside is saying
you have a critically ill daughter.
If this is true,
I'll divorce you!
And that damn key!
Back then, because of it,
we almost lost our lives!
Now you've forgotten the pain once the wound healed, haven't you?
You are right to scold me, my wife.
Absolutely right.
How many times have you promised me?
Let me tell you,
this time, no matter who comes,
you are not to get involved with this damn key!
Do you hear me?
Yes, yes.
Wife, my dear wife, rest assured.
I, your husband, swear
I will never let this thing worry you again.
And I absolutely will not
let anyone disrupt our peaceful life.
That's what you said.
If it happens one more time,
you pack your bags and get out!
Go find somewhere cool to stay!
I humbly obey my lady's command.
Then hurry up and make me some food!
That newly bought agarwood
is still waiting for you to make it into a zither.
You have too much free time!
What are you looking at?
Hurry up and leave!
Yes, Master.
From what I know,
this Qin Chi dislikes conflict,
but he is very stubborn.
It seems we can only succeed through wit this time.
My Lord.
That man is indeed the Qin Chi.
According to this subordinate's investigation,
the Qin Chi is henpecked.
The couple has been hiding in Dongyang City,
teaching the zither and students,
and staying out of worldly affairs for a long time.
Do you have an idea?
That depends on your skills, A Lan.
Me?
My wife!
Behold!
This divine craftsmanship!
How is my zither-making skill?
You're blowing your own horn to the heavens!
If it weren't for my painstaking efforts
to buy this agarwood back,
you, too, would be a skilled wife with no rice to cook!
Yes, yes.
Yes.
In this vast world,
only my wife loves her husband the most.
Heaven and Earth bear witness,
I will henceforth wash my hands and make soup,
keeping my wife away from trouble and strife,
bringing you joy every day.
Over here! Over here!
Master!
That girl from before brought someone with her!
This... what should we do?
This...
I'm sorry.
Didn't you tell me you were well hidden,
that they couldn't possibly find this place?
How was I to know they are this capable,
finding us so quickly?
You take that damn key right now
and throw it out for me!
Make them leave immediately!
No, that won't do!
Madam!
This Secret Key was entrusted to me
by the leader on his deathbed.
How can I casually hand it over to others?
You, a recluse,
forget about those damn rules!
Forget about past loyalties!
This... this...
This is not acceptable.
You won't throw that scourge
out for me, is that it?
Do you think you've lived too long, is that it?
Fine!
I'll give you a second choice.
You go out there yourself now
and persuade them to leave for me.
If, within half the time it takes to drink a cup of tea,
you cannot persuade them to leave,
do you remember what I told you?
Say it!
One more time,
pack your bags and get out!
Master's wife!
Why go to such extremes?
Isn't this putting Master in a difficult position?
Who knows what other tricks
those two outside have up their sleeves?
If he doesn't cherish his own life,
why should I stand here worrying for nothing?
What are you still standing here for?
Go chase them away!
My wife...
This...
Go, go, go!
Master's wife!
Wife, and you too!
Listen to me!
Out!
Wife, let me tell you...
Master! Master! Are you alright?
My nose!
Master!
They're back again!
They all seem to have gone mad!
Hurry up and catch them all for me!
I'm going right now!
Over there! Over there!
Hurry!
Heaven strike them dead!
Who is behind this mischief?
I'm going into labor!
They don't even spare people!
Truly ruthless to the extreme!
Heaven has sent down fiends!
Bringing calamity to this place!
This old man's integrity in his later years is ruined!
The demonic music backfired!
Master!
Your disciple is unfilial.
I... I must go first.
Disciple!
My disciple!
You actually stuffed cotton in there
You... you've gone too far
Senior Qin Chi
I've long heard of your great name
You... you...
You people
What deep-seated grudge do I have against you?
That you press me so relentlessly?
So vicious to this extent
How can you say that, sir?
I am your die-hard fan
That is, your admirer
I just wanted to pay you a visit
Enough with the nonsense
Your purpose for coming here
I know perfectly well
Why put on an act?
Since that's the case
Sir
Let's get straight to the point
The thing we want, to you sir,
is just a piece of scrap metal
But to us,
it concerns the nation's rise and fall
and the people's peace
We hope you will oblige us
Moreover,
Hasn't your wife always
been worried about you getting involved in trouble again?
Hand over that thing
and it can also return to you two
peace and safety
This thing involves too much
If it falls into the hands of villains,
the consequences would be endless
How can I know if you two have ulterior motives,
harboring ill intentions?
I beg your pardon, but this old man cannot grant your wish
Please leave
No...
You get out too, Shimu
Shimu
My wife
Who is your wife?
From now on, you can live with that stupid key of yours
My wife, my wife
Shimu
Shifu
Shimu says the time of half a cup of tea has passed
Since you insist on keeping that thing
and cannot extricate yourself from trouble,
the only way is a letter of divorce
to settle things cleanly from now on
Shimu
Oh, my wife
Why are you so heartless?
One day as husband and wife brings a hundred days of kindness
How decisive
Don't even need to go to the civil affairs bureau
Since it's come to this,
now that I'm all alone,
you can also forget about me handing over the secret key
This Qin Chi has quite a temper
Shifu
You still have me
Go, go, go away
Mr. Jiang
I have a way for you to return home
Shall we discuss a collaboration?
Shifu
What should we do?
I think that girl has a lot of clever ideas
Why not let them help us?
You want me to beg them?
I'd rather die
Then what should we do?
I've got it
Shifu
Do you remember when you first
proposed to Shimu?
How about this
They seem to have an idea
We'll see
There is a beauty, oh
Once seen, never forgotten
One day without seeing her, oh
I miss her like crazy
The phoenix soars high, oh
Searching the four seas for his mate
This...
What's this for?
Shifu
The storybooks all say
If we walk in the snow together,
we'll grow old together in this life
There's no snow,
so we have to use goose feathers instead
If we walk in the snow together,
we'll grow old together in this life
That's actually a good omen
My wife
Mr. Jiang
Are you sure you don't need my help?
Two acres and three-tenths of land
cannot compare to your unwavering devotion
From now on, I can only address you as "you" respectfully
Because you are in my heart
The Qixi Festival fireworks are very loud,
but not as much as I miss you
Dongyang City is actually trending
corny pick-up lines
Shifu
These sweet nothings
I gathered them from various popular
storybooks
When Shimu sees them,
she'll definitely be overjoyed
She's coming out
My wife
You finally agreed to...
What disgusting things did you write?
My wife
This...
Shifu
If all else fails,
let's use the final move
Shimu
Shifu says
if you don't open the door,
he will kneel outside
and never get up
If he wants to kneel, let him kneel
Shimu
Shifu is physically weak
He... he can't kneel for long
Shifu, please get up
Where did you find this washboard?
Shifu
Why... why are you doing this?
It seems Qin Chi truly is devoted to his wife
We'd better think of another way
Look
Shifu
For you
Master
Have some water.
If you faint,
Shimu will be heartbroken.
What an actor.
Master.
Please get up.
Look at you,
your face is all red.
If you faint,
Shimu will be heartbroken.
Quick, quick, quick!
Quick!
Master!
Wake up, Master!
Master, how could you faint, old man?
What's wrong, old man? Master!
Hurry, help your master inside!
Here.
Master.
Come on.
Take it slow.
You said you recently found a
long-lost, peerless qin score.
That's right.
I originally wanted to use this peerless score
to make a deal with Qin Chi.
But Qin Chi was unwilling.
This thing is useless to us now.
What a pity.
Destroy it.
What are you standing there for?
Help your master inside!
Master?
You...
It really is a peerless score?
You all...
You wretched old man!
How dare you trick me!
My wife!
I...
Get out of here!
If I ever let you back in this house,
I'll take your surname!
My wife!
I...
Oh, my wife!
Mr. Jiang,
we'll help you.